https://phaneuf.net/privacy-policy

Memorial Diamonds
A 21st Century Guide to Green Burials A 21st Century Guide to Green Burials
This incredible e-book explains green burial so that you can make informed decisions about your end-of-life arrangements. Learn what green burial and green cremation are, what products are available, and answers to commonly asked questions.
Download Now
Concierge Services
Video Streaming Services
About
Us
General Information
History
Staff
Video streaming service
By using our live video streaming, you can include everyone as part of the celebration of life, and they will feel like they are there with you.
Learn More
Obituaries
Blog
Send Flowers
News and Events
Customer Service: 1-800-742-6383
Privacy Policy
Information we gather
The following information is gathered from our website visitors:
IP address, email address and contact information (if you provide it), certain demographical information.
How we use the information we gather
We use the information to enhance your visitor experience.
The people that are given access to this information
Your personal information is accessible by the technology and the marketing departments.
The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information
To safeguard your personal information, all of our information is kept private and secure.
Use of Cookies
“Cookies” are small text files that a website transfers to a site visitor’s hard disk or browser for added functionality, or for tracking website usage. We do not use cookies to gather personal information, like a person’s name or e-mail address. In order to measure the effectiveness of our online presence, we may use cookies to identify repeat visitors to our web site, to determine the path visitors take on our site, and to identify visitors who came to our site as the result of a link on a third party web site. Any information gathered by the use of cookies is compiled on an aggregate, anonymous basis.
Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalize your experience of our website.
Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet. Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Privacy Policy & Disclaimers
Phaneuf Funeral Homes & Crematorium may publish obituaries on our web site that we have been asked to submit for publication to local/national media. In accordance with family wishes, information about services that families request remain private will not be published. We will honor any written requests from the decedentâ€™s legal next of kin to remove a published obituary.
We reserve the right to edit, or refuse to list, a condolence that contains language that is unlawful, harmful, fraudulent, threatening, abusive, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, profane, hateful, racially, ethnically, or otherwise objectionable, or encourages conduct that might constitute a criminal offense.
We reserve the right to change the information contained in this web site without notice. Our company is not responsible for any unintentional errors that may be contained in this web site. Links to other websites are provided for the convenience of the user and should not be construed as an endorsement of another web site or of the business referred to, or promoted, in another web site. We grant permission for any user to follow links to other web sites, but we cannot be held responsible for any content errors, copyright violations, libelous statements, offensive subject matter, or any other material that may be contained in those web sites, or in any succeeding web sites that may be reached by following those links.
We understand that privacy is an important issue for visitors to our web site. The following information is designed to help visitors understand what information we may gather from our site, and how we may use this information once it has been gathered.
Personal Information
Phaneuf Funeral Homes & Crematorium may collect personal information that site visitors provide when they complete any online form, application, or survey. Information provided in a request for service or information link/e-mail will be forwarded to one of our associates or affiliates so that a staff member can respond to the request. Phaneuf Funeral Homes & Crematorium may contact any visitor who has submitted a request for additional information, regarding the request. Our company is the sole proprietor of all data files gathered and we do not rent or sell visitors’ personal information to non-affiliate companies without the consent of the visitor.
Site Visitorship Data
Phaneuf Funeral Homes & Crematorium uses aggregated site visitorship data to improve the content and services offered to site visitors. All reports cite visitorship data on an aggregate, anonymous basis, which means that no personally identifiable information is associated with it. This data may include:
The number of people who visit our site
The pages they visit
The amount of time they stay on our site
The domain name of the site where visitors are connecting from (google.com for example)
The aggregate demographics (age/sex/interests) of our visitors
Google may use this data to provide search results and advertisements more likely to be of interest to viewers with similar, general characteristics. Phaneuf Funeral Homes & Crematorium may, in conjunction with the Remarketing and Similar Audiences features of Google, use this data to advertise to previous visitors to our website or audiences with similar aggregate characteristics to visitors to our website.
Online Advertising
This site uses Google Adwords, Google Remarketing with AdSense,  and Demographics and Interests Reporting.  This allows us to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to users who have visited the phaneuf.net site previously. This advertising could appear on a Google search engine results page (SERP) or another website in the Google Display Network.
Vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as Google advertising cookies) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
No personally identifiable information will be collected through the use of Google (or other third-party advertising and remarketing program) and any data collected will be used in accordance with our privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
Users may opt out of internet-based online advertising by visiting:http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. Opting out does not mean you will no longer receive online advertising. It does mean that the company or companies from which you opted out will no longer deliver ads tailored to your web preferences and usage patterns.
Security
If visitors submit credit card information in an on-line form, our company uses SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology to protect the information they submit. This technology protects visitors from having their information intercepted by anyone other than our company while it is being transmitted. Our company works hard to ensure that our systems are secure and that they meet industry standards. Where appropriate, we employ firewalls, encryption technology, user authentication systems (e.g., usernames and passwords) and access control mechanisms to control access to systems and data.
Hyperlinks
This web site contains hyperlinks or “links” to other sites, and other sites may “link” to this site. Web sites linking to and from this site may have different privacy practices from the ones described in this Privacy Policy and Disclaimer statement. Visitors to our site should read the privacy statements of other web sites they visit. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.
Changes to our Internet Privacy Policy
We may, from time to time, make changes to this policy. We recommend that visitors to this site revisit this privacy policy on occasion to learn of new privacy practices and changes to our policy.
This Internet Privacy Policy was last updated on June 15th, 2017. © Copyright 2015 Phaneuf Funeral Homes & Crematorium.
Sign up for our bimonthly newsletter
In our bimonthly email you’ll learn about upcoming events, grief resources and information to help you navigate the death-care industry.
Email*
NameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Five locations to serve you:Manchester, Boscawen, Littleton, NH& Brattleboro, VT
Toll-free: 1-800-PHANEUF
Phone: 603-625-5777
Email:
Fill out the form below with questions or comments. One of our caring staff members will respond to your inquiry as soon as possible.
×
